<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Instant Face Unlock</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">IFU</string>

    <string-array name="delay_array">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>1 Second</item>
        <item>2 Seconds</item>
        <item>3 Seconds</item>
        <item>5 Seconds</item>
        <item>10 Seconds</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_file">instant_unlock_settings</string>
    <string name="twitter">https://twitter.com/SamOfStenner</string>
    <string name="donate">https://paypal.me/samstenner</string>
    <string name="xda_thread">https://forum.xda-developers.com/xposed/modules/xposed-instant-unlock-t3688329#post74144137</string>

    <string name="info">
        • Enabled: Whether IFU is enabled or not\n\n
        • Fast: When enabled, the unlocking animation is skipped, making the unlock faster\n\n
        • Force Unlock: Will unlock regardless of what\'s on the lock screen\n\n
        • Allow Exceptions: Won\'t unlock if there are exceptions on the lock screen\n\n
        • Exceptions: Any kind of notification element\n\n
        • Music: If any media controller is active (such as Spotify or Google Play Music), auto-unlock won\'t activate\n\n
        • Dismissables: If there are notifications that can be dismissed, auto-unlock won\'t activate\n\n
        • Allow Non-Dismissables: Same as above, but if for non-dismissable notifications\n\n
        • Reveal Sensitive Notifications: Will reveal the content of a sensitive notification upon unlock.
          Enable hiding notifications in your phone\'s settings\n\n
        • Vibration: Will vibrate once the device is auto-unlocked\n\n
        • Duration: How long the vibration lasts in milliseconds\n\n
        • Delay: Will auto-unlock your device a specified number of seconds after face scan is completed
    </string>

    <string name="settings_reset">Preferences reset</string>

    <string name="sd_card_error">
        Instant Face Unlock has been installed on an SD card. In order to work properly, it must be moved onto your internal storage.
        However, because the app has been opened before you moved it, you need to uninstall it completely. Once it is installed again,
        move it from your SD card to your internal storage BEFORE doing a reboot. I hope to fix this in a future update, apologies
        for the inconvenience.
    </string>

</resources>
